<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on ZTCN.360</title>
    <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on ZTCN.360</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ztcn360.github.io/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Up the Town: Story of a Small Mobile Grocery Store</title>
      <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/rolling-up-the-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/rolling-up-the-town/</guid>
      <description>One of my pastimes is watching documentaries about culture and humanities. Among various channels, NHK’s documentaries never let me down. And the good thing is, some programs can be streamed within a certain period on NHK World. Recently, I have been obsessed with a program called “Hometown Stories” — stories about</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Turned My To-Do List Into a To-Read List</title>
      <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/i-turned-my-todoist-into-tore-toread-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/i-turned-my-todoist-into-tore-toread-list/</guid>
      <description>I have several experiences of trying some 100-day-challenges, and unfortunately, most of them failed. I switched to the 30-day-challenges, but I still failed. When I skipped one day, I quickly lost the passion for catching up on the next day. Such a vicious circle certainly dulls my motivation. It hurts.
At a certain point in my life (Actually, just yesterday), I made a pivot change in my To-Do list app (I use “Todoist”).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>优秀的产品与良好的心智模型</title>
      <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/what-is-a-good-product-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/what-is-a-good-product-design/</guid>
      <description>唐·诺曼（Donald A. Norman）是美国认知科学、人因过程等设计领域的著名学者， 也是著名的尼尔森诺曼集团（Nielsen Norman Group）的</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study of Enterprise Innovation in China: Xiaomi&#39;s Story</title>
      <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/xiaomis-innovation-story/xiaomis-innovation-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/xiaomis-innovation-story/xiaomis-innovation-story/</guid>
      <description>1. Background of the company Xiaomi was founded in 2010 by the Chinese entrepreneur Lei Jun, who believes that “high-quality technology doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to cost a fortune” (mi.com). Xiaomi has been successfully targeting at the domestic market, and ranked the fourth in China’s smartphone market</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[git push -u origin main] Doesn’t Work </title>
      <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/2022-05-02-git-push-u-origin-main-doesnt-%5Cwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/2022-05-02-git-push-u-origin-main-doesnt-%5Cwork/</guid>
      <description>Background: GitHub changed their default branch name from “master” to “main”, but strangely, git push -u origin main doesn’t work on my Mac. git push -u origin masterworks fine, but this command automatically creates an unnecessary “master” branch for me. I want to figure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Update This Blog</title>
      <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/2022-04-20-how-to-update-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/2022-04-20-how-to-update-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>This blog is built by Hugo and deployed to GitHub Pages. When updating new contents, I use Git pushing everything to the GitHub repository, and here are some memo to myself: #1 Write a post Open cmd, cd to hugo blog local folder. hugo new posts/“new post.md” Open “new po</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switch Between Multiple GitHub Accounts With SSH Keys</title>
      <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/2022-04-01-switch-between-multiple-github-accounts-with-ssh-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/2022-04-01-switch-between-multiple-github-accounts-with-ssh-keys/</guid>
      <description>The following are some commands I use frequently when I switch between different GitHub accounts on my Mac. Use the following command to set a default Git account: Git config –global user.name &amp;quot;username1&amp;quot; Git config –global user.email &amp;quot;useremail1&amp;quot; Use the following command to switch to another Git account temporarily. Git config user.name &amp;quot;username1&amp;quot; Git config user.email &amp;quot;useremail1&amp;quot; Use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/2022-03-20-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ztcn360.github.io/post/2022-03-20-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! Welcome to my blog. I built this blog for sharing my writings on design and tech innovation. Hope you find some posts useful. Feel free to get in touch!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
